http://www.area78.org/privacy

Skip over navigation
Information12ConceptsStepsTraditionsAA LinksACO HandbookArea GuidelinesTable OfficersAssembly OrientationCriteria for Hosting ACMGetting Started On Our WebsiteGSO CommuniquesAnonymity LetterGSO COVID-19Is AA For YouMapsPublic Service AnnouncementsThird Legacy ProcedureTravel AssistanceMeetingsRemoteDistrictsCommitteesArchivesCPCCorrection FacilitiesE ServicesGrapevineGroup RecordsLiteraturePublic InformationRemote CommunitiesTreatment FacilitiesBridging the GapCalendarCalendarPost An EventDownloadsGroup FormsPublic Download AreaTravel Assistance FormContact UsAA Help LinesArea ContributionsArea Service PositionsOnline FormsChange Email AddressCommittee Chair NominationVia EmailWebsite FeedbackAboutAbout UsDelegate PagePrivacy StatementWebsite Guidelines
About UsDelegate PagePrivacy StatementWebsite Guidelines
Privacy Statement
Area 78 Privacy Statement
Area 78 is committed to protecting your privacy as a visitor to this Website. To our visitors and to our members, we offer this pledge: We will not sell, disseminate, disclose, trade, transmit, transfer, share, lease or rent any personally identifiable information to any third party not specifically authorized by you to receive your information except as we have disclosed to you in this Privacy Policy.
Information Collection
When you send us email from this Website, you will provide us with certain personally identifiable information including your email address. At anytime, if you wish to no longer receive correspondences via email, please contact us via the address listed on our site under the “Contact Us” link.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data that is stored on a visitor's hard drive while they are visiting this Website. We may utilize a short-lived form of cookie when you visit this site. At Area 78 site, a cookie is only used to identify one unique visitor from another visitor during a particular session. A session is the period of active site-use while that unique visitor is linked to our server. We may use cookie technology during a session as a tool to carry forward your input information during the sign-in and authentication process. This enables the visitor to input their information once and have the information appear later during the session. No personally identifiable information is stored on the cookie. The cookie expires and is deleted from the visitor's computer as soon as they close their browser.
Third Party Links
This Website may contain links to third party Websites that are not controlled by Area 78. These third party links are made available to you as a convenience and you agree to use these links at your own risk. Please be aware that Area 78 is not responsible for the content of third party Websites linked to the Area 78 site nor are we responsible for the privacy policy or practices of third party Websites linked to the Area 78 site. Our Privacy Policy only applies to information we collect from you while you are at and while you are actively in a session with the Area 78 site. If you should link to a third party Website from the Area 78 site, we strongly encourage you to review and become familiar with that Website's privacy policy.
Changes In Our Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy without providing you with advance notice of our intent to make the changes.
If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact our E-Services committee chair using the online form on this link.
Home
Site Map
Search
Sign In
